The quiz gave you four file names and asked,
what's a single command that will delete the second
two while leaving the first two intact?
Now the first option, rm quote,
bad file quote, space quote,
good name bad face quote.
That'll work just fine.
It'll remove the two files we want to get while not touching the other two.
But it's kind of long.
That's a lot longer than the other options.
And the second one will remove every file whose name contains bad.
But that includes bad name good file which we wanted to keep.
So that option is not great.
The third one rm bad exclamation point good is not something that the shell understands.
It'll give you a weird error if you try it,
but it won't do anything terrible.
And the fourth one, rm star quotes bad space F quote star.
That will remove every file whose name contains bad space F which includes,
bad file and good name bad face.
Exactly what we want.
So the answer is that we can use either the first or the fourth option.
But I'd go with the fourth one because it's the shortest.